Guide to the Marilyn Horne Foundation Records, 1991-2011 CTC.2010.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Office Files, 1991-2010; I.
  - Development, 1993-2010; 3.
    - New York State Council on the Arts - Presenting program, 2007-2010 (Box 21, Folder 8-11)
    - New York State Council on the Arts - Radio production and broadcast, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
    - New York State Council on the Arts - Technology grant, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Finance, 1993-2010; 4.
    This subseries contains the files that pertain to the Marilyn Horne Foundation's finances. The subseries is split into two sections including accounting and audits as well as the Foundation's annual budgets. Both sections are filed and arranged in chronological order.
    - Accounting and Audits, 1994-2010
      - Accounting - Greef and Company, 1994-2010 (Box 22, Folder 1-7)
      - Audit 1994 - Bederson & Company CPA, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Audit 1995 - Lutz and Carr CPA, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Audits 1996, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Audits 1997 and 1998 - Lutz and Carr CPA, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
      - Audit FY99 - Greef & Company, LLC CPA, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Audits FY00, 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Audits FY00 - Internal Revenue Service, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Audits FY01, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Audit FY02 - Bederson & Company CPA, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Audits FY03-04, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
      - Audit FY05-06 - Bederson & Company CPA, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
      - Audits FY07-08, 2007-2009 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
      - Audit FY09-10 - Bederson & Company CPA, 2009-2010 (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
    - Budgets, 1993-2010
      - 1993/1994 Budgets and invoices, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - 1995 Budget and invoices, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - 1996 Budget and invoices, 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - 1997 Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - 1998 Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - 1999 Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Budget planning - FY01, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Budget planning - FY02, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Budget planning - FY03, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Budget planning - FY04, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Budget planning - FY05, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Budget planning - FY06, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Budget planning - FY07, 2006-2007 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Budget planning - FY08, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Budget planning - FY09, 2007-2009 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Budget planning - FY10, 2009-2010 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Foundation Office Files, 1993-2010; 5.
    This subseries contains the Foundation's general office files, which includes documents about the founding of the Marilyn Horne Foundation, reports, and information about Foundation's collaborations and venues. The files are arranged in alphabetical order.
    - 501(c)(3) status, 1993-2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Artist and presenter statistics, 1994-2009 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Artist inquiries, 1996-2007 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Auditions - April 21, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Auditions - December 13, 2000, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Auditions - 2002, 1999-2002 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
    - Auditions - 2004, 2000-2004 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
    - Auditions - March 25, 2006, 2002-2006 (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
    - Auditions - February 22, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Bertelsmann Music Group - Royalties, 1996-2008 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Broadcast Music Inc. - Licensing, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Bruce Yarnell Award for Young Artists, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Bylaws of the Marilyn Horne Foundation, 1995-2008 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Capital budget for establishment of Foundation office - Multiple proposals (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie Hall, 1998-2006 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Cecilia Bartoli - Special patron event, 1998-2000 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Corporate documents, 1996-2001 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Corporate documents, 1993-1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with political figures, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with President Bill Clinton and Senator Hilary Rodham Clinton, 1994-2004 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Donations in memory of Maurice Kasten, 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Dun & Bradstreet, 2004-2010 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Fact sheets, 1998-2006 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Five year history, 1993-1998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Foundation final reports, 2003-2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Furniture and equipment, 1998-2004 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - George Sape reception at the French Consulate, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Gerard Souzay, 1992-2004 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Guidelines for recitalists (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Harry Fox Agency, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Honolulu Symphony, 1998-2004 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Internship report by Cayce Travis - National Survey for Performing Arts Series Directors, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 15-16)
    - Items to be sent to local teachers or coordinators in the artist residency program (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Janice Mayer and Associates, LLC. - Auditions, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Kosciuszko Foundation - On Wings of Song partnership, 1998-2007 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Logo, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Materials for the Arts, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Merkin Concert Hall, 1995-2004 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Merkin Concert Hall Listening Room, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Mirshak Artists Management - Molly Fillmore audition, 2000-2005 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Moving costs for new office, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Musical America, 1995-2006 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - National residency program history, 1995-2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - National Survey for Performing Arts Series Directors - Results, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
    - Obituaries of opera performers, 2003-2007 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Planning checklist - Annual recital (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Program accomplishments, 1993-2006 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Program accomplishments outside of New York City, 1996-2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Progress report, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Royalties - The Song Continues book, 2003-2006 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Stationary (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Supertitles, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Van Cliburn Foundation, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer lawyers, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - White House - Proposed recital, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - William Paterson University, 2005-2010 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Marketing, 1993-2010; 6.
    The Marketing subseries contains a variety of materials that were used to promote the Foundation and its efforts including informational pamphlets, materials mailed to members, newspaper clippings, etc. The files are arranged in alphabetical order. Two items worth noting are a complete run of the Foundation's Sing On! newsletter and files detailing the planning and production of an educational video showing an introduction to classical song for a young audience.
    - Association of Music Personnel in Public Radio, 2001-2004 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Association of Music Personnel in Public Radio - Clearwater Conference, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Association of Music Personnel in Public Radio - Las Vegas Conference, 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Association of Music Personnel in Public Radio mailing, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Education program, 1999-2007 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Education video - Proposal, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Education video - What is a Classical Song?, 1997-2007 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Introduction to Marilyn Horne Foundation brochure, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Introduction and background of Marilyn Horne Foundation press release, 1998-2002 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Marilyn Horne Foundation press kit - Gladney Communications, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Marilyn Horne - Program biography, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Marketing pamphlets advertising Marilyn Horne Foundation events, 1993-2003 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Marketing pamphlets advertising Marilyn Horne Foundation events, 1999-2005 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1994-2003 (Box 33, Folder 2-11)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2004-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2007-2010 (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
    - Press kit for Marilyn Horne Foundation - Master copy, 1993-2005 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Saint Paul Sunday, 2001-2007 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Sample of foundation packet to be mailed to schools, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Save the date postcards for recitals and events, 1999-2010 (Box 36, Folder 4-14)
    - Sing On! Newsletters, 1995-2010 (Box 37, Folder 1-26)
    - Statements in support of the Marilyn Horne Foundation, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Supertitles, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Tenth anniversary CD project, 1993-2004 (Box 38, Folder 3-5)
    - Website, 2000-2007 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
  - National Residencies, 1992-2010; 7.
    The Marilyn Horne Foundation sponsored residencies for artists all over the country. Young artists were featured in an educational program, which was followed by a recital for pre-college students. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by name. There are also files for each school or festival which contain correspondence with the venues, contracts, marketing information, programs, budgets, etc. The students and teachers were sometimes surveyed after their performances; these surveys are filed at the end of each school's residency folder.
    - Ames Town & Gown Chamber Music Association, 1997-2005 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
    - Ames Town & Gown Chamber Music Association, 2005-2007 (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
    - Astral Artistic Services, 1997-2001 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Athenaeum Music and Arts Library of La Jolla California, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Austin Peay State University / Clarksville Community Concert, 2002-2008 (Box 41, Folder 1-12)
    - Bach Festival Society of Winter Park Florida, 2006-2009 (Box 42, Folder 1-6)
    - Baldwin-Wallace College Art Song Festival, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Barrier Island Group for the Arts, 1999-2002 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
    - Barrier Island Group for the Arts, 2002-2007 (Box 43, Folder 1-7)
    - Brownville Concert Series, 1998-2001 (Box 43, Folder 8-11)
    - Brownville Concert Series, 2002-2009 (Box 44, Folder 1-10)
    - Brownville Concert Series - Final report and surveys, 2006-2009 (Box 45, Folder 1-5)
    - Cal Performances - University of California at Berkeley, 1995-1999 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Cape and Islands Chamber Music Festival, 1994-2002 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Celebrity Series of Boston, 1998-2002 (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
    - Celebrity Series of Boston, 2003-2005 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
    - Central Florida Cultural Endeavors Inc., 1999-2003 (Box 47, Folder 3-6)
    - City of Los Angeles Department of Cultural Affairs, 1999-2005 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Cleveland Institute Art Song Festival, 1992-2006 (Box 48, Folder 3-6)
    - Connecticut Grand Opera & Orchestra, 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Crossroads Arts Council, 2001-2003 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Forth Worth Opera, 2004-2008 (Box 49, Folder 3-6)
    - George Mason University Institute of the Arts, 1992-1998 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Georgia Southern University Department of Music, 2004-2007 (Box 50, Folder 1-4)
    - Glenridge Performing Arts Center, 2004-2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Grace Note Music Series, 1998-2003 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Hill and Hollow Music, 1998-2004 (Box 50, Folder 7-10)
    - Huntsville Chamber Music Guild, 1997-2007 (Box 51, Folder 1-10)
    - Huntsville Chamber Music Guild, 2005-2010 (Box 52, Folder 1-6)
    - International Music Foundation, 2007-2008 (Box 52, Folder 7-8)
    - Juneau Jazz & Classics, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy Center, 1994-2001 (Box 53, Folder 2-3)
    - Kravis Center for the Performing Arts, 2002-2004 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Michigan State University East Lansing, 1997-2002 (Box 54, Folder 2-3)
    - Middlebury College Concert Series, 1996-1997 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Middlebury College Concert Series, 1998-2002 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Mozart Society of California and Da Camera Society of Mount St. Mary's College, 1994-2006 (Box 55, Folder 2-5)
    - Munson Williams Proctor Institute, 1995-1999 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - Munson Williams Proctor Institute, 2000-2006 (Box 56, Folder 1-8)
    - New Jersey Symphony Orchestra, 1998-2004 (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
    - Oberlin Conservatory, 2006-2010 (Box 57, Folder 1-5)
    - Palladium Theater, 2000-2006 (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
    - Palm Springs Desert Museum, 1994-1999 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Penn State Center for the Performing Arts, 2001-2006 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
    - Philadelphia Chamber Music Society, 1994-2001 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Saint Louis Arts Museum, 2006-2009 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Saint Mary's College, 1997-2000 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Santa Barbara Choral Society, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 2006-2009 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
    - Santa Fe Concert Association, 2008-2009 (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
    - Santa Monica College, 2000-2010 (Box 59, Folder 6-7)
    - Skirball Cultural Center, 1995-2002 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Southeastern Louisiana University, 1996-2004 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - Southeastern Louisiana University, 1997-2009 (Box 61, Folder 1-8)
    - Southeastern Louisiana University - Final report and surveys, 2007-2009 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    - State University of New York Buffalo, 1998-2009 (Box 62, Folder 3-10)
    - State University of New York Buffalo - Final report and surveys, 2006-2009 (Box 63, Folder 1-9)
    - University of Arkansas Little Rock / Art Spree, 1997-2008 (Box 64, Folder 1-12)
    - University of Denver Newman Center, 2002-2006 (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
    - University of Louisville, 2007-2009 (Box 65, Folder 6-8)
    - University of Pittsburgh at Bradford, 2001-2008 (Box 66, Folder 1-5)
    - University of Pittsburgh at Bradford, 2008-2010 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - University of Pittsburgh at Bradford - Final reports and surveys, 2004-2009 (Box 68, Folder 1-8)
    - Virginia Arts Festival, 1998-2003 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - Vocal Arts Society, 1995-2001 (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
    - Vocal Arts Society, 2002-2010 (Box 70, Folder 1-10)
    - Vocal Arts Society - Final report and surveys, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
    - William Jewell College, 1994-2005 (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
  - New York City Education Programs, 1999-2010; 8.
    The Marilyn Horne Foundation participated in several New York City area educational programs. The Foundation partnered with several New York City schools and the Education Through Music program, whose aim was to promote the integration of music into the curriculum of disadvantaged schools. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by folder title. There are files for each school that contain the surveys that were conducted after the performance.
    - Children's Aid Society Chorus - Final report and surveys, 2005-2007 (Box 71, Folder 5-8)
    - Education program, 1999-2003 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Education program - Manhattan Center, 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Education programs: Fall '05 through Spring '06 - Final reports and surveys, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Education Through Music, 2000-2005 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Education Through Music - Partner schools, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Education Through Music - Student comments, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Education Through Music - Training seminar, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Educational outreach, 1999-2000 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Humanities and the Arts High School - Final report and surveys, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Internship report by Jiyeon Park - 2002-2003 New York City Education Program (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - LaGuardia High School - Final report and surveys, 2006-2008 (Box 72, Folder 8-10)
    - LaGuardia High School - Final report and surveys, 2009-2010 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - Public School 3 - Final report and surveys, 2005-2008 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Public School 38 - Final report and surveys, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Public School 43 - Final report and surveys, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Public School 68 - Final report and surveys, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Public School 69 - Final report and surveys, 2006-2008 (Box 73, Folder 7-8)
    - Public School 76 - Final report and surveys, 2006-2008 (Box 73, Folder 9-11)
    - Public School 83 - Final report and surveys, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Public School 102 - Final report and surveys, 2004-2008 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Public School 155 - Final report and surveys, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Saint Ann's School - Final report and surveys, 2004-2008 (Box 73, Folder 15-17)
    - Saint Ann's School - Thank you cards from children (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Saint Anselm School - Final report and surveys, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Saint Anthanasius School - Final report and surveys, 2007 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Saint Anthony School - Final report and surveys, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Saint Brendan School - Final report and surveys, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Saint Clare - Final report and surveys, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 5-7)
    - Saint Stephen of Hungary School - Final report and surveys, 2006 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - School of the Blessed Sacrament - Final report and surveys, 2004-2007 (Box 74, Folder 9-11)
    - School program guidelines (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Wadleigh School - Final report and surveys, 2009-2010 (Box 74, Folder 13-14)
- Programs and Events, 1993-2011; II.
  This series contains materials on the programs and events of the Marilyn Horne Foundation. It is divided into four subseries: Benefits and Other Events; the Music Academy of the West; On Wings of Song recital series; and the Song Continues Annual Event.
  - Benefits and Other Events, 1994-2009; 1.
    This series contains planning materials on several benefits and fund raising events that were held by the Marilyn Horne Foundation. Materials include correspondence, financial papers, invitations, programs, and other materials.
    - Appreciation dinner - Nadine Bognar and Marilyn Horne Foundation Trustees, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Champagne reception - In honor of Nadine Bognar and Jeanne Thayer, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 2-3)
    - Cultivation events, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Dinner - Marie Nugent-Head, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Marilyn Horne Foundation benefit - San Francisco, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 6-9)
    - Marilyn Horne Foundation benefit - New York City, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Marilyn Horne Mediterranean Music Cruise, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Marilyn Horne Mediterranean Music Cruise - Travel dynamics, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 2-3)
    - New York Times Company Foundation luncheon, 1998-1999 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Patron open house, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Sony Corporation event - New York City, 1999-2000 (Box 76, Folder 6-7)
    - Sony Corporation event - New York City, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Music Academy of the West, 1997-2009; 2.
    The Music Academy of the West is an institution which, like the Marilyn Horne Foundation, is committed to the development of the next generation of classical musicians. Marilyn Horne, who studied under Lotte Lehmann at the Academy as a teenager, accepted the position of Voice Program Director in 1997 and consequently the two groups have been in close collaboration ever since. This subseries contains materials for each of the Music Academy of the West's Summer Festivals between 1997 and 2009. Each year's folders contain correspondence, financial papers, reviews, advertising, programs, and other materials.
    - Summer Festivals 1997-2000 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Summer Festival 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Summer Festival 2002 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Summer Festival 2003 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Summer Festival 2004 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Summer Festival 2005, 2005-2006 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Summer Festival 2006 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Summer Festival 2007 (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
    - Summer Festival 2008 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Summer Festival 2009, 2008-2009 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - On Wings of Song, 1994-2010; 3.
    On Wings of Song is the Marilyn Horne Foundation's monthly vocal recital program which features young artists. Many of these recitals were later broadcast on New York City's WQXR radio station. For several years the performances were also brodcast of the Chicago station WFMT. This subseries is arranged chronologically. Within each year, there are files on the artists for that season, programs, marketing information, commissions, and other materials.
    - 1995-1996 Season
      - Artists, 1995-1996 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Feedback, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Press, 1995-1997 (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
      - Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Startup, 1994-1995 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - 1996-1997 Season
      - Artists, 1995-1997 (Box 80, Folder 7-8)
      - Programs, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 1997-1998 Season
      - Artists, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - On Wings of Song radio syndication, 1995-1998 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 1998-1999 Season
      - Artists, 1997-1999 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Programs, 1998-1999 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 1999-2000 Season
      - Artists, 1999-2000 (Box 81, Folder 7-8)
      - Guest lists, 1999-2000 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - 2000-2001 Season
      - Artists, 2000-2001 (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
      - Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Radio syndication, 2000-2001 (Box 82, Folder 6-7)
      - WQXR broadcasts, 2000-2001 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - 2001-2002 Season
      - Artists, 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 2-3)
      - Programs, 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Recital compilation - CD project, 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 5-6)
      - Song cycle commission - Lowell Liebermann, 2001-2002 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - WQXR broadcasts and advertising, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - 2002-2003 Season
      - Artists, 2002-2003 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - General season information, 2002-2003 (Box 84, Folder 4-6)
      - Kosciuszko Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Programs, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Radio syndication, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Song commission - Paul Moravec, 2003-2005 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - WQXR broadcasts, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - 2003-2004 Season
      - Artists, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - General season information, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 7-9)
      - Marketing, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Programs, 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - 2004-2005 Season
      - Artists and general season information, 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 3-4)
      - Programs, 2004-2005 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - 2005-2006 Season
      - Artists and general season information, 2005-2006 (Box 87, Folder 2-3)
      - Marketing, 2005-2006 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Programs, 2005-2006 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - 2006-2007 Season
      - Artists and general season information, 2006-2007 (Box 87, Folder 6-7)
      - On Wings of Song radio syndication, 2004-2007 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
      - Programs, 2006-2007 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 2007-2008 Season
      - Artists and general season information, 2007-2008 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Papering, 2002-2008 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Ticket sales, 2007-2008 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - 2008-2009 Season
      - Artists and general season information, 2008-2009 (Box 89, Folder 2)